✔ F-47: the REPL idle hint is terminal text, not a path, and survives intact (1.2853ms)
✔ F-47: a bare slash — between spaces, at end of text, alone — is not a path (0.8011ms)
✔ F-47: every real POSIX path the reviewer named still redacts (0.4282ms)
✔ F-47: protocol-relative // stays untouched, as before the narrowing (0.1118ms)
✔ F-47: the Windows-path branch is untouched and still redacts (0.1768ms)
✔ F-47: the credential-name branch is untouched and still redacts (0.1442ms)
✔ F-47 mutation control: restoring the broad rule re-redacts the hint, and only the hint tests notice (1.047ms)
✔ F-27: completed delegation is stored and projected with both honesty fields (20.5266ms)
✔ F-27: refused write retains its own reason durably (12.2486ms)
✔ F-27: nondelegated unreadable panes are named, using observePanes (5.3692ms)
✔ F-27: redactions and truncation survive projection; names/host paths do not (5.7519ms)
✔ F-27: repeat render and deletion/reprojection preserve bytes and store (14.6801ms)
✔ F-27: install root and sibling-prefix containment, with no store write on refusal (6.4636ms)
✔ F-27: cap is explicit and deterministic, with later history retained in store (49.8ms)
✔ F-27: overcommitted observePanes floor never exceeds the shared budget (7.7812ms)
✔ F-27: store absence and drift fail closed; journal bytes cannot become authority (8.67ms)
✔ F-27 mutation control: omitting self_published is detected by the decisive assertion (1.1856ms)
✔ F-27: projection rechecks privacy on a readable store entry (0.2299ms)
✔ F-27: a failed journal write remains visible without changing the pane gate result (0.2511ms)
ℹ tests 19
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 19
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 240.6211
